{
    "subject": "resource/Faiz_Ahmad_Faiz",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Progressive_Writers'_Movement",
    "human_readable": "Faiz Ahmad Faiz was associated with the Progressive Writers' Movement.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9613450169563293,
            "question": "Which progressive movement did Faiz Ahmad Faiz contribute to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9489765167236328,
            "question": "What literary movement was Faiz Ahmad Faiz associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8922531604766846,
            "question": "Name the movement that Faiz Ahmad Faiz was part of."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8505395650863647,
            "question": "In which literary movement did Faiz Ahmad Faiz play a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8246247172355652,
            "question": "Faiz Ahmad Faiz is known for his work in which literary movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7639133334159851,
            "question": "What was Faiz Ahmad Faiz's involvement in the literary world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7428869605064392,
            "question": "What kind of writer was Faiz Ahmad Faiz known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845340490341187,
            "question": "What was the Progressive Writers' Movement all about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5381883382797241,
            "question": "Can you describe Faiz Ahmad Faiz's contribution to literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4511297941207886,
            "question": "To which intellectual and artistic group did Faiz Ahmad Faiz belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Faiz Ahmad Faiz was associated with the Progressive Writers' Movement.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8719_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe Faiz Ahmad Faiz's contribution to literature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8719_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the Progressive Writers' Movement all about?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8719_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of writer was Faiz Ahmad Faiz known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8719_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8719_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provide information about Faiz Ahmad Faiz's membership and secretaryship in the Progressive Writers' Movement (e.g., \"Faiz started a branch of Progressive Writers' Movement in Punjab in 1936. Also he was a Member and Secretary of this branch.\")"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Faiz Ahmed Faiz started a branch of the Progressive Writers' Movement in Punjab in 1936 and served as its member, secretary, and editor. This clearly indicates his association with the movement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}